Long ago, humans rejected Melusines, and Melusines feared humans
Uzun zaman önce, insanlar Melusinaları reddeder, Melusinalar da insanlardan korkardı.
There was one Melusine who became fascinated with human medicine
İnsan tıbbına ilgi duyan bir Melusina vardı
But no human wanted her help
ancak insanlar onun yardımını istemedi.
And there was one girl who liked Melusines
Bir de Melusinaları seven bir kız vardı, o yüzden insanlar onunla arkadaş olmazdı.
So, the Melusine became the girl's friend
O yüzden Melusina bu kızla arkadaş oldu
And the girl became the Melusine's "patient"
ve bu kız da Melusinanın "hasta"sı oluverdi.
Your checkup's all done. You're still in perfect health
Tüm muayenelerin tamam. Sağlığın gayet yerinde.
Thank you, Doctor Melusine!
Teşekkürler Doktor Melusina!
In this game of doctor and patient, a friendship was born
Bu doktor hasta oyunu sayesinde bir dostluk peyda oldu.
Then one day, the girl fell ill
Sonra bir gün kız bir hastalığa yakalandı.
The Melusine was the only doctor to arrive on time
Melusina, zamanında yetişen tek doktor olmasına rağmen yetişkinler onu orada istemediler.
Scram! Melusines can't be trusted!
Git buradan! Melusinalara güven olmaz!
So just because I'm not human... I can't save my best friend?
Yani sırf insan değilim diye... Dostumu kurtaramayacak mıyım?
In desperation, the Melusine approached the frightening witch
Melusina çaresizlik içinde korkunç cadıya yaklaştı
She begged, and begged, until she got a reply
ve ondan bir cevap alana dek durmadan yalvardı.
If you take this potion, concocted of sin
Günahla harmanlanmış bu iksiri alırsan
You will gain a human face and grow human limbs
insan yüzü ve uzuvları kazanacaksın,
But then, you will lose everything that attracted this friend of yours to you in the first place
ancak sonrasında, ilk başta arkadaşının sana ilgi duymasını sağlayan her şeyini yitirmiş olacaksın.
Can you accept that?
Bunu kabul edebilir misin?
The Melusine did not hesitate for very long
Melusina çok tereddüt etmedi.
On a rainy night, a little doctor knocked on the girl's door
Yağmurlu bir gecede, küçük bir doktor kızın kapısını çaldı.
The doctor wore a hood and raincoat
Doktorun başında kapüşon, üstünde de yağmurluk vardı.
Maybe to protect her from the rain... but maybe also to hide a secret
Bu belki kızı korumak içindi... Belki de bir sırrı gizlemek için.
The little doctor held the girl's hand and treated her illness
Küçük doktor kızın elini tuttu
Dawn came, and the little girl's condition improved
Şafak sökerken kızın durumu artık daha iyiydi,
But the little doctor was long gone
ancak küçük doktor çoktan gitmişti
For she knew her friend would never recognize her again
çünkü artık dostunun onu tanıyamayacağını biliyordu.